calculator.com 2006-06-15

# Privacy Statement calculator.com - Online mortgage math loan finance scientific health & sports calculators

|    

|   |  |  | **Top |  Privacy Statement **  
---|---  
  
|  calculator.com is not a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. Though we obide by the rules and policies 100% we can not afford to pay them the requiered licensing fees. 

**Information Collection** calculator.com is the sole owner of the information collected on calculator.com. calculator.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

**Profiling** We do NOT profile our visitors in any way.  
  
---  
  
**Cookies** A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We do not use cookies on calculator.com at this time. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies,you should check the respective privacy statements for more info. Look at [bCentral](http://www.bcentral.com/help/policy/privacy.asp) and [Tribal Fusion](http://tribalfusion.com/www/about/privacy.html). 

**Links** This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, calculator.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Third Party Intermediaries** We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for donations, goods and services. These company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Please view their Privacy Statement at [iBill](http://ibill.com/about/privacy.cfm).   
  
**Log Files** Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We also look to what visitors are searching for so we can write the calculators that our visitors want the most. 

**Newsletter** If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask only for an email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out at any time.We support a NO SPAM policy. We do not sell, exchange or otherwise give out, our subscriber list. Subscribers can not post to this mailing list.
